We will move to Earth's horizon.
We will find infinity for sure.
Let's save all this blue sea and
let the wind Take us far away!
Don't give up.
So I can come back to this moment.
So I can be present right here.
Throw away this drop.
Sometimes we share.
Shut it up!
Do not be so afraid to podcast.
To have a friend right here.
And I will always be here by your side.
To take care of you.
Even in the darkest of times.
I'll try looking brave.
It's alright now.
Cause we are the ones who
are meant to rule them all.
We will move to our same horizon.
We will find insanity for sure.
We're a world from our head.
We will win for sure.
Dreaming on.
We will move to the worst day horizon.
We will fight however we can.
In order to be the best we will run.
To the top, to the end.
We gotta be the world.
Cause just keep dreaming on.
I just can't give up now.
I can never stop cause.
I gotta give everything I got to.
Think of the greatest of all times.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will find infinite fortunes.
We will step ahead.
We will wait for sure.
So keep moving on.
Whoa!
Move in and capture Straw Hat Luffy!
Bring it on!
Channel the Hock!
Blow through my body!
I got you!
No!
I'm gonna send you to hell!
Man, I was still off!
How did I do it?
Hitting Kaido with Haki from
the outside isn't gonna cut it!
I can't just hit the target.
I have to let Haki flow into it.
It's not power, it's control.
Kaido's scales are too
tough to just punch.
This is the only way I can break through.
Crap, it's still way too much.
Don't screw with me.
That punch didn't feel right either.
Come here!
Need you guys to line up
so I can figure this out!
I'll master Ryo and Knight!
Let's go!
That thing gets Mr. Straw Hat down.
Look at him go!
Chopper Emon, shall we make our way down?
Uh-huh!
Let's go and rescue Olin!
Huh?
Rescue who now?
Forget about that lady!
In fact, I'm glad that we lost her!
Loopy Daddy needs help.
Leave her, Kiku.
Why isn't he trying to run
yet? Let's go! All right.
Warden, what if the prisoners rebel?
Shouldn't we get them back in
their cells while we still can?
Get on it.
I'm impressed.
He's sticking it to him.
He's crazy strong. It's unreal.
I'm thinking we should
make a break for it.
Right.
Most of the guards have taken off.
Now's our chance.
I know what to do.
One poison drives out another, right?
Go and get ready, Difugo.
I'm making the call. Oh, yeah? You sure?
All right.
Attention, inmates! Listen up!
This is an order!
Your friend Lufitato is a wild animal
who wants to tear this prison apart.
And you are going to bring him to heal.
What's that guy talking about?
If you still refuse to fall in line,
you all know what comes next. Boo!
Go!
If you want to live through this,
then capture Luffy Toto this instant!
Oh, come on!
Do you actually think that this will work?
These guys aren't gonna listen to you!
Stop it! Let me go!
Don't you want to ask him?
I want your side, you bunch of dopes!
Listen, it's not like we're
rooting for the guards here.
We don't want to do this, but
we don't have much of a choice.
We've got our hopes up that
we saw you fight back there.
But even if we do manage
to break out of here,
Orochi's still in charge,
so what's the point?
Besides that, we already tried to revenge
Lord Odin once and ended up in here.
That bastard Kaido's way too tough.
Plus, we've lost our
families and comrades, too.
He's beaten us into submission
with little hope for the future.
Seeing you fight back was amazing,
but Lord Yasui's execution brought back
all that fear and despair from before.
Even if we do manage to break out of here,
what's the point when we'll
just be homeless and starving?
The people of Wano will
never be free again,
so we might as well just give up already.
Wise decision.
You'll obey us if you don't want to die.
Just let them go, you selfish jerk!
You're the one who's being selfish! Huh?
As an outsider from overseas, you
can run and fight all you like.
but that's your choice to make!
You can't expect us to
back you up! We're tired!
Please, have mercy!
Don't give us false hope!
That's just so cruel!
You guys!
Are you all right?
We're going to get you help, okay?
Really?
You sure about that?
I think you should worry more
about yourself than each other.
I'm burning! It's hot!
Someone help me! Hang on.
You're going to be fine.
What's this green crab?
I told you what happened
if you stepped out alive.
What I just fired at you was
a highly contagious play.
One touch and you're
going to get infected.
Let those poor bastards
serve as an example in case
the rest of you decide you
want to try something funny.
You see, Master Queen has a hobby
of creating weapons and viruses.
This is just a taste of what he can do.
It's burning.
these are master queen's special
playgrounds who else wants to test them out
Straw Hat i can't help but wonder why you
thought the prisoners
would ever rally behind
you their will to resist dried up long ago
and you're about to suffer
along with them like
hell i am i dare you to try and shoot me
didn't you hear what i
said you can get infected
by those around you
even if i don't hit you
everyone listen you guys gotta spread out
what does it matter so what if we die
here maybe it's for the best i can't
explain right now but trust me i can fix
things for you say your prayers Straw Hat
Don't hold back,
Straw Hat Boy Be their beacon of hope
Let them know the fire of rebellion
still burns We've been given one
last chance Kaido can be defeated
I heard a voice coming from
the never-opening cell Guess
he's still kicking after all
There's a person in there?
I thought it was a beast.
I forgot.
No one told you what was inside.
It's no man and it's no animal, but
it's proven to be quite the monster.
The plan was to keep
feeding him fish from the
factory's polluted water
runoff until he died in agony.
But he was quite resilient, as those
orders came from the Shogun 13 years ago.
It was intended to be a slow and
painful death, but he hung on.
Honestly, we let this
go on for far too long.
The prisoner inside of that cell is
none other than one of the Akazaya Nine!
Are you joking?
But I thought they all died out long ago.
Finish the job!
We'll call it an accidental death!
That laugh!
No question, it's Kawamatsu!
Wait for me!
I'm on my way!
Would you take a look at this guy?
That slimy little freak is a
member of the famous Akazaya 9?
He's mine, boys!
You tricked me!
The hell? A needle?
Maybe a fishbone?
Slime will protect me!
This is bad.
The huge-headed guy got away.
Kabatsu!
Your keys and your sword are incoming!
Impeccable timing. I'm grateful.
Been far too long, my trusty old blade.
Sotomousso.
So tell me.
Do you like sumo wrestling?
Kawamatsu!
Don't worry.
I'm on my way.
Everyone ready?
Here I go!
Akariwa!
Ah!
Oh, what the hell?
Still just as tough.
Remember, Kawamatsu, you lose
if your feet leave the ground.
That technique...
things were.
Gotcha now!
A flash of steel at the
blowing rapids of a river.
They call it Kappa style.
River of Retribution!
Do you think I found those
poisonous fish a delicacy?
No, rather they were so vile that my
innards twisted and begged for mercy.
Yet, I stood firm for 13 years.
Compared to my lord's suffering,
it was barely a drop in a pond.
Long have I waited, but the time has come.
Kawamatsu the Kappa has
joined this epic crusade.
Kawamatsu!
Kiku! Ugh.
You haven't changed a bit.
I'm so glad that you are free.
Raizo, same to you. Huh?
Kiku, you're here too?
What's going on?
Anyone know who the short
guy with a swollen head is?
He's an intruder, sir.
The man who stole the sword and cup
keys, I don't know how he got in here.
Hey, don't just stand there.
Do something about him, sir.
I gave you orders.
Why the heck did you turn back?
Kawamatsu.
Are you feeling better?
Get it all out.
My apologies.
That was 13 years of bad fish.
Get the playgrounds ready to fire!
Finish them off before
this gets out of hand!
Everyone prepare for battle!
I demand you release Sir Luffy!
Daddy Oh kiku!
Rise!
Oh hey!
Don't tell me your boss yogurt!
Oh I am!
However, it's you who should speak up!
Why don't you tell them
who you really are?
If you want to inspire
those with broken spirits,
you must remove your disguise
and reveal your identities!
They once fought for our cause, so
I'm certain their passion will return!
How true!
Splendid idea!
I agree as well!
Let's earn their trust before proceeding!
Listen close!
We are not mere ghosts or memories!
The legends are true!
No way! That mask!
It belongs to the most beautiful
swordsman in all of Wano.
I thought he died at Oden Castle.
Could it really be Kiku
Nojo of the Fallen Snow?
Huh?
Wait, you're a guy?
I am a woman at my heart.
The mask, yikes!
Hold up.
That's Fukurokuju's rival
ninja, Raizo of the Mist.
Samurai there is the most
powerful sumo wrestler ever.
Yokozuna Kawamatsu!
And the old man is who
we suspected all along.
He's Yoguro the Flower!
One question, though.
Who is this Luffy Taro guy?
Who cares about that? He is incredible!
Hey! It's me!
This leads me to believe Lord
Orochi's ramblings were true!
We've got to report this
to Commander Kaido somehow!
Nay.
Now that you have seen us, thy
lips must be sealed forevermore.
Now, attack!
Nico, flower shooting kid!
Heavy gun!
Come, come! Got me!
Okay, try these playgrounds.
Oh, no.
We keep missing him with the bullets, sir!
What do we do?
I told you, hit someone close to us!
You bastards!
Why don't you fight me?
They've suffered enough!
Fighting with a virus is
the lowest of the low!
You gotta go to us first
to get to the general.
Let's break through, chopper! On it!
Now, gong gong!
Heavy! He's dead!
Leave my comrades alone!
I second that!
It's a demon!
Kappa style.
Norikiri.
Ninpou, lightning shuriken!
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha.
For you, friends of Sir Luffy.
We're not friends.
One of those should set you free.
Hmm, killer.
I've been shot!
It burns! It burns!
Help!
It's some people!
Stay away from me!
This is pissing me off!
The prisoners don't deserve this!
Oh, yeah! That's right!
You have no idea what horror awaits you.
The plague starts with a burning
sensation from the bullet wound.
Then the pain spreads to every corner of
your body until your blood bursts out.
The victim is left in agony, twisting
and crawling in search of relief.
And in doing so, they infect
anyone they come in contact with.
Ah! Ah!
Great mercy!
Stop!
Ah!
Wouldn't you look at that?
A perfect example of
how this stuff spreads!
Oh!
Save me!
You ever see a human being
shrivel up like that?
They look like a bunch
of rotting old weeds!
Do something.
Back up or you'll infect me.
Nice, huh?
It's called the mummy play. Get it?
It truly is.
Master queens.
Finest work!
Go!
Now all of you are human weapons!
One little touch and you
can share your suffering!
Don't take another step closer to us!
You'll spread the virus even more!
Just give me some time!
I'll find a cure for you, I promise!
Sure you want to oppose me?
You know what happens
to rebels, don't you?
Careful!
Seems they have no choice.
We're in trouble.
All of Udon Prison is fighting against us!
Escape all you can!
and you shouldn't have come here.
We don't want your help.
None of this sort of habit now.
We're all doomed.
It doesn't matter if you're
the legendary Akisaya samurai.
They outpower us in every way.
It's pointless.
No matter how you look
at it, you'll never win.
Why bother?
You're up against the worst of the worst.
The dragon who blacks out the sky.
Plus he has the beast
pirates to back him up.
No one stands a chance against them.
Please just take a look around you.
All of this chaos unleashed
by one weapon made by.
one of Kaido's men,
utter devastation, utter despair,
and Kaido never raised a finger.
If you outsiders hadn't invaded, at least
we could have carried on with our lives.
Even if it was miserable,
it wasn't like this.
We weren't past the point of no return.
We didn't have to suffer this nightmare,
watching our own bodies shrivel
up and eat themselves alive.
Don't touch them, Lufitaro! You'll die!
Stop this crap right now!
No way!
Hey, he'll be infected too!
You guys can't convince me!
Is he crazy?
Are you trying to kill yourself?
Sarno Future, why would you do this?
Mr. Straw Hat!
You guys can't convince me!
You think this tower can't be beat?
You're just giving up!
It can't hurt me at all!
I'm okay!
You see?
Stupid liar!
You gotta get away from this now!
Please, Luffy!
They're trying to break your
spirit, but you gotta listen!
Samurai I met are really tough!
They're fighting for you!
Everyone has to pull together!
You talk about your life here!
Like slaving away for dumplings is a life.
You give it just enough
so you don't keel over!
You think that's what life is about?
Look around you, a bunch of slaves.
You're worth more!
Huh?
Big Bro and his friends are okay!
Is he, though?
And so what if I'm not
from the land of Wano?
Big deal!
Why is it so wrong to
get help from me, huh?
I made a promise I got to keep.
I have a friend named Tama.
She made sure I could eat even
when she had nothing herself.
So I owe it to her to make this country a
place where she can fill
her belly every day.
I'm going to make this a normal thing.
I swear that by the time we leave Wano,
it'll be a place where you can
eat as much as you want every day.
I refuse to fail.
Because if I do, you'll be trapped
in this living hell forever.
Now, help me!
I have already heard about Odin.
Sounds like an amazing guy.
But when Kaido killed him 20 years ago,
everything in this country
came to a complete standstill.
I shouldn't have to remind you.
Trust me and my friends.
We'll beat Kaido.
That's why we're here.
There's no reason for our own
allies to stand in our way!
So make up your minds right now!
Are you guys with us?
Or are you with Kaido?
You really mean it?
Truly, you're not lying.
You're giving this another shot.
He's winning everyone over, that
man can sure capture a heart,
it seems like you guys
are going weak on me, huh?
No matter, I can still sway you to
my side with a little crowd control.
Just one shot in the middle, then
everything will turn to chaos again.
Time to break out the big one—how
does 200 times the amount sound?
sound Here comes your plague shot!
Take this!
A plague-packed elephant smart shoe!
Please don't do this, warden!
Please have mercy on us!
Mercy on us!
Hey, Baba Nuki's going to
fire something this way. What?
It's too late.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Elephant smart shoe!
Now sneeze smart shoe!
Ha-ha!
Ha-ha! No! Wait!
Had to do it.
The future I saw took a bad turn.
Oh, oh!
Oh!
Ah, let it go, no game!
Oh, no!
Incredible.
What a capable fellow!
Handle the rest for me.
Leave it to us. Hang on a sec.
I'm in charge. Take it over.
Remember what happens to
anyone who defies a jailer.
First defense is you lose your arms.
We know, but we don't care.
Call us rebels, but
we've had enough of you!
You're gonna pay for
our years of suffering!
Get her! Yeah!
Eight days remain before
the great battle begins.
The enemy's main forces
are still oblivious.
Udon has been conquered. Mr. Straw Hat!
That was magnificent!
I have to admit you found
one hell of an ally.
Thank you, Kin'emon.